Family over everything.
Shadow Force is a action, thriller film directed by Joe Carnahan.
Kyrah and Isaac were once the leaders of a multinational
special forces group called Shadow Force.
They broke the rules by falling in love, and in order to
protect their son, they go underground.
With a large bounty on their heads, and the vengeful Shadow Force hot
on their trail, one family's fight becomes all-out war.
Kyrah, played by Kerry Washington.
Isaac, played by Omar Sy.
Ky Sarr, played by Jahleel Kamara.
Jack Cinder, played by Mark Strong.
Auntie, played by Da'Vine Joy Randolph.
Unc, played by Method Man.
Shadow Force is a 2025 American action thriller film directed by Joe
Carnahan and co-written by Carnahan and Leon Chills.
It stars Kerry Washington, Omar Sy, Mark Strong, Da'Vine
Joy Randolph, and Cliff "Method Man" Smith.
Shadow Force was released theatrically by Lionsgate on May 9, 2025, two days following Lionsgate's
split from Starz, making it the first film to be released under the new Lionsgate Studios.
It received negative reviews from critics and performed poorly at the box
office, grossing only $5 million against a $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of espionage, spy, son,
special forces, hunter are hunted.
The tone is intense.